officegamespot.com 2019-08-16

# OfficeGameSpot Privacy Policy

| 

## **Last Updated: March 10, 2019**  
  
---  
  
## At Officegamespot.com, the privacy of our visitors is important. This privacy policy outlines the types of information that can be received and collected by this website and how it is used.  
  
## **Introduction:**  
  
## This Privacy Policy applies to your use of the Officegamespot website. We only access information which is absolutely necessary to the functioning of the web site and we do not share, rent or sell this information to any third parties.

Consenting to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy when you first visit our website permits us to use cookies every time you visit our website.

Officegamespot does not actively run a user registration system, forum, chat or instant messaging function and thereby does not directly collect any personally identifiable information about our users except for persistent identifiers (cookies) used in our advertising operations as noted below. Some games featured or hosted on Officegamespot that are managed by third-party publishers may contain features such as user registration systems, forums, chat rooms and so forth; which are not managed by Officegamespot and are dictated by the privacy policy of the game's publisher.  
  
## **Personal Information We Receive or Collect:**  
  
## We don’t request or require you to provide personal information to access our web site. As explained below, we may receive your IP address and user agent automatically. If you optionally elect to fill out our newsletter form, we will receive your email address.  
  
## **How We Use The Information Collected:**  
  
## 1\. We use aggregate information to understand how many total users have visited our web site.  
2\. We use information you choose to provide in our web forms to send an email newsletter.  
  
## **Local Shared Objects:**  
  
## Certain games on Officegamespot will create "Local shared objects" which allow the game to save game progress so that when you return you can pick up from where you left off. These save files are usually stored on your own computer and not shared with any third parties. However for games that are multi-player or include the use of a server with a user account system, this data may instead be stored in a cloud-based service. In this instance, storage and retrieval of such data is dictated by the privacy policy of such game publisher offering the service.  
  
## **The Information We Collect:**  
  
## We limit the information we collect only to what’s necessary to insure the website operates correctly. You are not required to sign-up, register or provide personal information about yourself in order to use our web site.

When you use our web site, we collect the following information:

**Internet Protocol Address (“IP address”)**. IP addresses are assigned by your Internet service provider to the modem used to access the Internet for connected devices in your home and/or work-place. Any devices using the modem to access the Internet may broadcast the same IP address. At home, connected devices could include one or more laptop/desktop computers, tablets, mobile phones, smart/connected TVs and gaming consoles. At work, connected devices could include one (or all) floor(s) in an office building.

**User Agent**. Due to the nature of how the Internet works, we may receive information (known as “User Agent”) automatically sent by your web browser, such as data associated with the source device’s Internet browser/content delivery software (e.g., Microsoft Explorer, Mozilla Firefox or Google Chrome). The User Agent information we receive may also include information such as device type (e.g., computer, tablet, mobile device), and/or date/time of visit.

**Email Address (optional)**. If you use the information provided on the Officegamespot.com website to contact us directly we will receive your contact information, but will only use it in order to respond to your inquiry. If you fill out a web form on our web site we receive your email and may store that email address for up to 12 months. Information, such as your email address, that you enter in order to set up subscriptions to our emails and/or newsletters are stored until you unsubscribe.  
  
## **How We Collect Information:**  
  
## We collect information when you visit our web site.

**IP address**. Our web site receives IP address from your Internet-browser (e.g., Microsoft Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome) each time you request a file or web page.

**User Agent**. Similar to the collection of IP address, our web site also receive User Agent information associated with your browser (e.g., Microsoft Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, etc.) and type of device (e.g., whether the device is running a Windows or Apple operating system.)

**Email Address (optional)**. Email addresses are collected for distribution of our newsletter for subscribers only. If you choose to contact us directly with an inquiry using the contact information available to you on the Officegamespot.com website, we will receive your contact information and use it to provide you with a response.  
  
## **How We Use the Information We Collect:**  
  
## **IP addresses** – Fraud Prevention  
Our use of IP addresses is limited to helping identify and combat potentially fraudulent activity. IP addresses are stored in our log-files and are deleted after 30 days.

**Respond to Inquiries**  
If you choose to contact us directly using the contact information we provide on the Officegamespot.com website, we will use your contact information to respond to your inquiry.

**Email Newsletter (optional)**  
We use an email address for sending you our email newsletter, if you have requested it (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require the newsletter).  
  
## **Disclosing Personal Information:**  
  
## We will not rent, sell or share information about you. We will not, without your express consent, supply your personal information to any third party. Your Personal Information will only be disclosed where required or allowable by law.  
  
## **Advertising:**  
  
## Officegamespot is a free to use website and generates revenue through third-party advertising on the website. These third-party advertising companies may collect and use information about your visits to this and other websites to help determine which advertisements are most suited to your interests and measure performance of any advertising campaigns. In order to collect this information, the third-party may use a cookie or other such methods including javascript codes. Officegamespot has no influence over the policies of third-party advertising networks (except our ability to discontinue using their services).

The information they collect may be considered personally identifiable, or it could be considered personally identifiable in certain circumstances. This information is only ever used for our legitimate business interests and will never be sold or shared by us.

Nevertheless, the data is provided to us by third parties. While we use all reasonable commercial endeavours to ensure that they adhere to any applicable laws, we encourage you to familiarise yourself with their data policies.

If you would like more information about advertising practices and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can visit Google's Advertising and Privacy page:  
http://www.google.com.au/policies/technologies/ads/   
  
## **Cookies and Web Beacons:**  
  
## Officegamespot does not use cookies, however some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include: CPMStar

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on this website send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

This website has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. This website’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.  
  
## **Opt Out of Targeted Advertising on Officegamespot.com:**  
  
## Targeted advertising using browser behaviour is designed to ensure users see more relevant advertising based on their interests. If you prefer not to see targeted advertising from our advertising partners you can opt out of these services, or find out more information about their privacy policies by following the below links:   

## **CPMStar:**  

## **Security of Your Personal Information:**  
  
## We do not require you to provide personal information to use our web site. Still, ensuring the information collected by our web site is secure and protected is very important to us. Your Personal Information is stored in a manner that reasonably protects it from misuse, loss, unauthorized access, modification or disclosure. 

We store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall-protected) servers.

You acknowledge that the transmission of information over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.  
  
## **Updating Information:**  
  
## You have the right to access the data Officegamespot holds about you and to update and/or correct it, subject to certain exceptions.

If you wish to access, update, or delete your Personal Information, please contact us. We may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request. In some cases, we may have to keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes.  
  
## **Data Retention:**  
  
## Officegamespot will retain your data only as necessary for our legitimate business interests, such as to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

If you contact us directly using the contact information or form provided on the Officegamespot.com website, we will retain your contact information as long as necessary in order respond to your inquiry. We may retain copies of these communications for a period of up to twelve months. After that, the communications will be deleted from our system, unless we are required by law to retain it longer.  
  
## **Third Party Websites:**  
  
## Officegamespot may link to other web sites and is not responsible for the content or privacy policies of these external sites. Some games on Officegamespot also contain links to external sites or may contain requests for personal information for gameplay purposes (e.g. account registration or chatroom features) which are governed by their own individual privacy policies. All users should therefore also be aware of the individual privacy policies within any game that requests personal information such as name or email address.  
  
## **How to Contact Us:**  
  
## If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us at this email address:  
privacy@officegamespot.com  
  
## **Changes to This Privacy Policy:**  
  
## We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time based on changes to applicable laws and regulations or other requirements applicable to us, changes in technology, or changes to our business. Any changes we make to the Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page, so you should review it periodically.
